





**ABOUT ME** 

I am an Artificial Intelligence MSc graduate with experience in working with Deep Learning, Computer Vision, and Time Series Analysis in the medical domain. **SKILLS** 

Pytorch (Lightning) / Tensorboard / Slurm / Pandas / scikit-learn / pytest / gRPC / ONNX / H5PY / OpenSlide / NLTK / spaCy / Gensim / Docker / Singularity

**EXPERIENCE** 

11/2021 - Now Deep Learning Researcher

Medis Medical Imaging

I researched, developed, and validated production-ready computer vision algorithms (Deep Learning-based and otherwise) for echocardiography workflow automation, and maintained and developed inference and evaluation infrastructure.

Pytorch (Lightning) / Slurm / scikit-learn / gRPC / ONNX / Docker

5/2021 – 7/2021 Artificial Intelligence Analyst

The Netherlands Cancer Institute

I investigated Deep Learning-based methods for outcome prediction of Ductal Carcinoma in Situ (DCIS) from pathology whole glide images (VCIs)

(DCIS) from pathology whole-slide images (WSIs). Pytorch / Slurm / Docker / Singularity

11/2019 - 4/2021

internship

Research Intern

The Netherlands Cancer Institute

Researched and developed a computational pipeline for predicting outcome of DCIS from WSIs.

Pytorch / Slurm / Docker / Singularity

6/2019 Research Intern

KPN

internship NLP and Data Mining project in collaboration with the University of Amsterdam.

scikit-learn / NLTK / spaCy / Gensim

3/2018 - 6/2018 **Teaching Assistant** 

University of Groningen

I assisted teaching for the BSc Neural Networks course at the University of Groningen.

3/2018 - 8/2018

Research Intern

Universitair Medisch Centrum Groningen

I analysed biometric signals to perform early detection of sepsis in ICU patients.

scikit-learn

**EDUCATION** 

2018 - 2021 MSc in Artificial Intelligence (Cum Laude)

University of Amsterdam

I presented an abstract on my thesis *Multiple-Instance Learning for Assessing Prognosis of Ductal Carcinoma In Situ* at the European Congress of Pathology of 2021. Follow-up research based on

my work was accepted at SPIE 2022.

2015 - 2018

BSc in Artificial Intelligence (Honours in Philosophy)

University of Groningen

I presented a paper resulting from my thesis on *Early Detection of Sepsis Induced Deterioration Using Machine Learning* at the BENELEARN2018 conference, and the paper was published in the

conference proceedings.

**SOFT SKILLS** 

**LANGUAGES** 

**HOBBIES** 

I am organized, detail oriented, good at team building, and verbal communication.

English - C2 Italian - C2 I love cooking, playing bass, sailing, and martial arts